

Personal

Name Mustafa Şahin

Address

Mevlana Mahallesi Anafartalar Caddesi Çiğ Sokak No:13 Daire:3 Ataşehir/ISTANBUL istanbul

Phone number 0534 438 99 86

Email

mustafasahin.developer@gmail.com

Website

Github: https://github.com/mtfsahin Web site: www.mustafasahin.dev

LinkedIn

https://bit.ly/3E65WIR

Languages

English B2

Mustafa Şahin

I have been working as a freelance software developer for more than 1 year. As a freelance software developer, I gained experience in various programming languages such as

React Native , JavaScript(frontend) , Rest-API (php) and 3D modeling in Blender environment. Lately, I've been experiencing React Js , Node Js and Angulartechnologies. I gained experience in python - iGraph and text processing in the works I did for my graduation project. I am passionate about research, education and training.

Github: https://github.com/mtfsahin **Web site**: https://mustafasahin.dev/

Work experience

Freelance sofware developer

Sep 2021 - Present

Freelance, Malatya

I gained experience in various programming languages such as

React Native ,JavaScript ,Rest-API (php) and 3D modeling in Blender environment.

Intern Oct 2018 - Mar 2019

Mavitech B.V, bursa

I have experienced the working logic of ERP systems and how they are used in the field.

Intern Aug 2018 - Oct 2018

Biz-med, istanbul

I gained experience about C# programming language, I also experienced hospital technologies.

Education and Qualifications

Lisans - Computer engineering 2019 - 2022

İnönü Üniversitesi, Malatya

Gano: 3.01

Önlisans - Computer programming

2016 - 2019

Bursa Uludağ Üniversitesi, Bursa

Gano: 3,25 I also saw English preparation.

References

Prof.Dr. ALİ KARCI

Skills

Java

React Native

JavaScript

3D Modelling

2D drawing (illustrator-Photoshop-Figma)

Python

Node Js - Angular